<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AboutMe</string>
    <string name="name">Joseph Aguele</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star string resource</string>
    <string name="bio">Some people say that the best way to improve public health is by increasing the number of sports facilities. Others, however, say that this would have little effect on public health and that other measures are required.
 Discuss both these views and give your own opinion.\n\n
Give reasons for your answer and include any relevant examples from your own knowledge or experience. Write at least 250 words.

\n\nIt is normally being said that health is wealth. This calls for the need to provide a functional health care system for the people of any society. But can we say that the best way to improve public health is by increasing the number of sports facilities? Or will this have little effect on the health of the masses? In this essay, I will show that although purchasing more sports facilities is germane to having good public health, it is not the best way of improving the health condition of the people of any society since there are other substantive measures that must be put in place.
\n Increasing the number of sports facilities in a residential environment has a good impact on the overall health conditions of the residents. Setting up more sports facilities: Gyms with cutting edge technology, sports centres etc. where people can spend their leisure time, does some good to the health of any people. For example, people will be encouraged to use the gyms for training, fitness and other activities to help keep the body in a good shape. Young people will use sports centres like football pitches, basketball courts, long tennis and other sports for keeping themselves active and sharp.  However, this cannot be said to be the best way of handling public health issues because of the little effect it has on the people.
\nThe best ways to improve public health include and is not limited to: providing good medical centres that are free or affordable for the common man, ensuring that people practice personal hygiene. Other ways of improving public health would be educating the public about substance abuse and its destructive consequences which has eaten deep into the lives of young adults. Moreover, setting up effective drainage and waste disposal systems also curb the introduction of deadly insects like Mosquitoes within a residential environment.  All of these are much more important that increasing sport facilities in any vicinity.
\nIn conclusion, increasing the number of sports facilities is important since it has its own role to play in improving public health. But it should clearly known that this is not the best approach to improving public health, neither can it be a substitute for providing affordable medical centres. The populace should be educated about the need to keep themselves healthy. The idea that increasing sport facilities is best in improving public health is manifestly ridiculous.


</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nick_name">What is your nick name?</string>
</resources>
